(Adapted from the novel "Counterattack" by Chai Ji Dan)
(مقتبس من رواية "هجوم مضاد" للكاتب تشاي جي دان)
(Episode 12, Why Doesn't He Play By the Rules?)
(الحلقة 12، لماذا لا يلعب حسب القواعد؟)
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
This way, you'll feel less nervous.
بهذه الطريقة، سوف تشعر بتوتر أقل.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
Don't tell me...
لا تخبرني...
Call me Hubby.
اتصل بي زوجي.
No.
لا.
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Let's have breakfast.
دعونا نتناول وجبة الإفطار.
Let me help you up.
دعني أساعدك.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I can get up myself.
أنا أستطيع النهوض بنفسي.
Slowly.
ببطء.
Have some breakfast.
تناول بعض وجبة الإفطار.
Sit down.
اجلس.
I prepared breakfast for you.
لقد أعددت لك وجبة الإفطار.
Make sure you nourish yourself.
تأكد من تغذية نفسك.
I'm afraid you can't take it after only a few times.
أخشى أنك لن تتمكن من تحمل ذلك بعد بضع مرات فقط.
Here.
هنا.
Try this.
جرب هذا.
- Tonight... - Today,
- الليلة... - اليوم،
I want to go home.
أريد أن أذهب إلى المنزل.
My mom misses me.
أمي تفتقدني.
My mom really misses me.
أمي تفتقدني حقًا.
Okay.
تمام.
After you finish breakfast,
بعد الانتهاء من وجبة الإفطار،
I'll drive you home.
سأوصلك إلى المنزل.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I can go home by myself.
أستطيع أن أعود إلى المنزل بنفسي.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Can't I tell what you're thinking?
هل يمكنني أن أقول ما الذي تفكر فيه؟
Teacher.
مدرس.
Pick up the phone.
التقط الهاتف.
I miss you so much.
أفتقدك كثيرًا.
I really want to talk to you.
أريد حقًا التحدث معك.
(Jiang Xiao Shuai)
(جيانغ شياو شواي)
What exactly are you doing?
ماذا تفعل بالضبط؟
This won't do.
هذا لن يفعل.
I'm going to look for him.
سأبحث عنه.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Where's Dr. Xiao Shuai?
أين الدكتور شياو شواي؟
He hasn't made a house call for days.
لم يأتي إلى المنزل منذ أيام.
He hasn't made house calls for days?
لم يقوم بزيارة المنازل منذ أيام؟
Where did he go?
أين ذهب؟
When I went to his house to look for him,
عندما ذهبت إلى منزله للبحث عنه،
his neighbor said the same thing,
وقال جاره نفس الشيء،
that he hasn't been home for days.
أنه لم يكن في المنزل منذ أيام.
He came in the middle of the night.
لقد جاء في منتصف الليل.
One night, after 2am,
في إحدى الليالي، بعد الساعة الثانية صباحًا،
I saw him standing alone in front of the clinic.
رأيته واقفًا وحيدًا أمام العيادة.
At first, I thought he was a thief.
في البداية، اعتقدت أنه كان لصًا.
He was all covered up.
لقد كان مغطى بالكامل.
It turned out to be Dr. Jiang himself.
اتضح أنه الدكتور جيانج نفسه.
He came in the middle of the night?
هل جاء في منتصف الليل؟
What is he up to?
ماذا يفعل؟
You even know how to make desserts?
هل تعرف حتى كيفية صنع الحلويات؟
I also made the late-night snack...
لقد قمت أيضًا بإعداد وجبة خفيفة في وقت متأخر من الليل ...
you had last night.
لقد كان لديك الليلة الماضية.
So you've made yourself...
لقد صنعت نفسك...
into such an all-rounder...
إلى مثل هذا اللاعب متعدد المهارات...
just to have fun with men?
فقط للاستمتاع مع الرجال؟
Ever since I was little,
منذ أن كنت صغيرا،
my parents wanted a daughter.
أراد والدي أن يكون لديّ ابنة.
But they only had me.
لكنهم كانوا يملكونني وحدي.
So ever since I was little,
لذلك منذ أن كنت صغيرا،
they raised me as a daughter.
لقد ربوني كابنة.
They wanted me to learn how to play music and chess,
لقد أرادوا مني أن أتعلم العزف على الموسيقى والشطرنج،
do calligraphy, and embroidery.
أمارس فن الخط والتطريز.
You've always treated yourself like a girl?
هل تعاملت مع نفسك دائمًا كفتاة؟
Believe it or not,
صدق أو لا تصدق،
I'll show you what a man is.
سأريك ما هو الرجل.
It's quite interesting...
إنه أمر مثير للاهتمام للغاية...
to see you get mad.
أن أراك غاضبًا.
None of those men...
لا أحد من هؤلاء الرجال...
in the past...
في الماضي...
has tried my cooking.
لقد جرب طبخي.
Then who has?
إذن من لديه؟
Their next boyfriend.
صديقهم القادم.
Chi Cheng.
تشي تشنغ.
Yes.
نعم.
It seems like you care a lot about him.
يبدو أنك تهتمين به كثيرًا.
Of course.
بالطبع.
After all, we grew up together.
في نهاية المطاف، لقد نشأنا معًا.
Later,
لاحقاً،
he's even coming to visit.
حتى أنه سيأتي لزيارتي.
Please don't tell him that I'm staying here.
من فضلك لا تخبره أنني سأبقى هنا.
I'm begging you. Please don't.
أنا أتوسل إليك. من فضلك لا تفعل.
Xiao Shuai, I can't take it anymore.
شياو شواي، لا أستطيع أن أتحمل ذلك بعد الآن.
Please come home earlier tomorrow.
من فضلك تعال إلى المنزل مبكرًا غدًا.
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
Lower your voice.
أخفض صوتك
I'm going to check my computer.
سأقوم بفحص جهاز الكمبيوتر الخاص بي.
Don't make a sound.
لا تصدر صوتا.
Hey.
يا.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
you're coming back to your own clinic.
أنت تعود إلى عيادتك الخاصة.
Why are you acting like a thief?
لماذا تتصرف مثل اللص؟
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
If Wu Suo Wei finds out,
إذا اكتشف وو سو وي،
then Chi Cheng will know.
ثم سوف يعرف تشي تشنغ.
I can't be too careful.
لا يمكنني أن أكون حذرا للغاية.
Okay.
تمام.
Essence?
جوهر؟
On the surface, you look gentle and refined.
ظاهريًا، تبدو لطيفًا وأنيقًا.
I didn't expect...
لم أتوقع...
Yes.
نعم.
Go back to our place tonight.
عد إلى مكاننا الليلة.
I suddenly miss my mom.
أفتقد أمي فجأة.
I want to spend one more day with her.
أريد أن أقضي يوما آخر معها.
Now that you mention it,
الآن بعد أن ذكرت ذلك،
I haven't been back for a long time.
لم أعود منذ فترة طويلة.
I'll go home with you.
سأذهب معك إلى المنزل.
Don't.
لا.
When you go back,
عندما تعود،
my mom will be suspicious.
أمي ستكون مشبوهة.
Of what?
من ماذا؟
Are you afraid your mom...
هل أنت خائفة من أمك...
will be able to tell that I slept with you?
هل سيكون بوسعي أن أقول أنني نمت معك؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Xiao Shuai.
شياو شواي.
Why aren't you back yet?
لماذا لم تعودي بعد؟
Does he really sneak back in the middle of the night,
هل يتسلل حقا في منتصف الليل؟
and don't turn on the lights?
ولا تشغل الأضواء؟
Teacher.
مدرس.
Did you reject me for two nights...
هل رفضتني ليلتين...
just to hug him?
فقط لعناقه؟
Why is it you?
لماذا انت؟
Did I disappoint you?
هل خيبت ظنك؟
I...
أنا...
No.
لا.
What are you doing? Don't move.
ماذا تفعل؟ لا تتحرك.
Stay still.
ابقى ساكنا.
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
Why is the door open?
لماذا الباب مفتوح؟
Is there a thief?
هل هناك لص؟
How dare he steal from me?
كيف يجرؤ على سرقتي؟
Does he have a death wish?
هل لديه رغبة في الموت؟
I'll kill you!
سأقتلك!
Why are you still here?
لماذا مازلت هنا؟
Do you want to join us?
هل تريد الانضمام إلينا؟
No.
لا.
Sorry to bother you.
آسف لإزعاجك.
Carry on.
حمل.
Continue.
يكمل.
Why am I so unlucky?
لماذا أنا سيئة الحظ؟
Why do I keep bumping into them?
لماذا أستمر في الاصطدام بهم؟
They...
هم...
They've already...
لقد فعلوا ذلك بالفعل...
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
I'm doomed.
لقد حُكم علي بالهلاك.
I'm too ashamed to meet my master this time.
أنا أشعر بالخجل الشديد من مقابلة سيدي هذه المرة.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
Go and pack up.
اذهب وحزم أمتعتك.
Move into our house.
انتقل إلى منزلنا.
But we'll still see each other.
ولكننا سنظل نرى بعضنا البعض.
My dignity as a man...
كرامتي كرجل...
Is your dignity as a man...
هل كرامتك كرجل...
reflected by meeting him at night?
هل ينعكس ذلك من خلال لقائه في الليل؟
Do you think I want to see him at night?
هل تعتقد أنني أريد رؤيته في الليل؟
He's been avoiding me.
لقد كان يتجنبني.
Ask around. He hasn't made house calls for days.
اسألوا حوله. لم يقم بزيارة منزلية منذ أيام.
I can only wait for him here at night.
لا أستطيع إلا انتظاره هنا في الليل.
When was the last time you talked to him?
متى كانت آخر مرة تحدثت معه؟
Maybe a week ago.
ربما منذ اسبوع.
It's the sixth day.
إنه اليوم السادس.
Sixth day?
اليوم السادس؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Give me your phone.
أعطني هاتفك.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'll even the score for you.
سأعادل النتيجة لك.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Teacher.
مدرس.
Actually, Guo Cheng Yu...
في الواقع، قوه تشينغ يو...
knew about it a long time ago.
عرفت ذلك منذ زمن طويل.
Guo Cheng Yu!
قوه تشينغ يو!
Come out, Guo Cheng Yu!
اخرج، قوه تشينغ يو!
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
You...
أنت...
Why are you dressed like that?
لماذا ترتدي مثل هذه الملابس؟
I just took a shower.
لقد استحممت للتو.
Isn't that normal?
أليس هذا طبيعيا؟
Why did you come to see me at this hour?
لماذا أتيت لرؤيتي في هذا الوقت؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Well...
حسنًا...
I'll get going.
سأذهب.
You didn't come here for anything,
لم تأتي إلى هنا من أجل أي شيء،
but I need something from you.
ولكنني أحتاج إلى شيء منك.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
I found something interesting...
لقد وجدت شيئا مثيرا للاهتمام...
in your drawer.
في درجك.
For example,
على سبيل المثال،
this aphrodisiac essence.
هذا الجوهر المثير للشهوة الجنسية.
I really like it.
أنا حقا أحب ذلك.
- Give it to me. - No.
- أعطني إياه. - لا.
- No...
- لا...
No.
لا.
I'm... I'm sorry.
أنا... أنا آسف.
I... I didn't do it on purpose.
أنا... لم أفعل ذلك عمدًا.
Meng Tao.
منغ تاو.
Meng Tao, don't.
منغ تاو، لا تفعل ذلك.
Why are you doing this to me?
لماذا تفعل بي هذا؟
Meng Tao.
منغ تاو.
I feel hot.
أشعر بالحر.
Don't do this.
لا تفعل هذا.
Don't act this way.
لا تتصرف بهذه الطريقة.
Don't be like this.
لا تكن هكذا.
Apart from a slight headache,
بصرف النظر عن الصداع الطفيف،
I don't really feel unwell.
أنا لا أشعر بتوعك حقًا.
(Drink some when you wake up, it's good for the stomach)
(اشرب القليل منه عند الاستيقاظ فهو مفيد للمعدة)
Mrs. Wu.
السيدة وو.
Mrs. Wu, what's wrong? Are you unwell?
سيدتي وو، ما بك؟ هل أنتِ مريضة؟
I'm fine. This happens all the time.
أنا بخير. هذا يحدث دائمًا.
Xiao Chi, what brings you here today?
شياو تشي، ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا اليوم؟
I bought some supplements for you,
لقد اشتريت لك بعض المكملات الغذائية،
so I brought them over.
لذلك أحضرتهم.
Look at you. You always bring something when you come.
انظر إلى نفسك، أنت دائمًا تحمل شيئًا ما عندما تأتي.
All right. Let's talk inside.
حسناً، لنتحدث في الداخل.
Mrs. Wu.
السيدة وو.
Let's go. I'll take you to the hospital.
هيا بنا، سآخذك إلى المستشفى.
- Come on. - It's okay.
- تعال. - لا بأس.
I just need to take some medicine.
أحتاج فقط إلى تناول بعض الأدوية.
Your health is important. Let's do a checkup.
صحتك مهمة. لنجري فحصًا.
- Mrs. Wu, slowly. - Okay.
- السيدة وو، ببطء. - حسنًا.
So...
لذا...
you've been staying...
لقد بقيت...
at Guo Cheng Yu's place in the past few days?
في مكان Guo Cheng Yu في الأيام القليلة الماضية؟
Guo Cheng Yu is a troublemaker.
قوه تشنغ يو هو مثير للمشاكل.
If it weren't for him,
لو لم يكن هو،
I would have completed my mission.
لقد اكملت مهمتي.
He even purposely told me...
حتى أنه قال لي عمدا...
that you two didn't sleep together.
أنكما لم تناميا معًا.
So I only dared to stay at his place.
لذلك لم أجرؤ إلا على البقاء في مكانه.
Mission?
مهمة؟
What mission?
ما هي المهمة؟
You still don't know?
هل مازلت لا تعرف؟
Forget it. I'll be honest with you.
انسي الأمر، سأكون صادقًا معك.
Chi Cheng gave me an ultimatum...
لقد أعطاني تشي تشنغ إنذارًا نهائيًا...
to let you willingly...
لأسمح لك طوعا...
sleep with him within five days.
النوم معه خلال خمسة أيام.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
I'll be the one in trouble.
أنا سوف أكون الشخص الذي يقع في المتاعب.
In the end, I didn't accomplish it.
في النهاية لم أتمكن من تحقيق ذلك.
I didn't dare to contact you either.
ولم أجرؤ على الاتصال بك أيضًا.
Chi Cheng told you to set me up?
هل قال لك تشي تشنغ أن تضبطني؟
Da Wei.
دا وي.
You're not mad at me, are you?
أنت لست غاضبًا مني، أليس كذلك؟
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I can't blame you.
لا أستطيع أن ألومك.
After all, you were forced to do it.
بعد كل شيء، كنت مجبراً على القيام بذلك.
If I were you, I wouldn't be able to handle it either.
لو كنت مكانك، فلن أكون قادرًا على التعامل مع الأمر أيضًا.
I just regret it.
أنا فقط نادم على ذلك.
Why did I fall for it so easily?
لماذا وقعت في الفخ بسهولة؟
The two of us...
نحن الاثنان...
are just small fries.
هي مجرد بطاطس صغيرة.
Chi Cheng is a big fish.
تشي تشنغ سمكة كبيرة.
Guo Cheng Yu...
قوه تشينغ يو ...
is an old fox.
هو ثعلب عجوز.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Should I take this opportunity...
هل يجب أن أغتنم هذه الفرصة...
to tell him why I approached him back then?
لأخبره لماذا اقتربت منه في ذلك الوقت؟
This way, he'll apologize,
بهذه الطريقة سوف يعتذر
and I'll admit to my mistake.
وسأعترف بخطئي.
We're even now.
نحن متعادلون الآن.
This is indeed a good opportunity.
وهذه فرصة جيدة بالفعل.
After getting rid of this mental struggle,
بعد التخلص من هذا الصراع العقلي،
you'll have nothing to worry about.
لن يكون لديك ما يدعو للقلق.
In the past few days...
في الأيام القليلة الماضية...
that you've been staying at Guo Cheng Yu's house,
أنك كنت تقيم في منزل Guo Cheng Yu،
didn't you two...
ألم تفعلوا ذلك؟
Don't overthink it.
لا تفكر كثيرا في الأمر.
We didn't.
لم نفعل ذلك.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I don't think...
لا أعتقد...
Guo Cheng Yu likes me.
قوه تشينغ يو معجب بي.
When you asked him for the snake,
عندما طلبت منه الثعبان،
he just gave it to you without hesitation.
لقد أعطاك إياه دون تردد.
When I was injured,
عندما أصبت،
he didn't take the chance to snatch the snakes either.
ولم يغتنم الفرصة لانتزاع الثعابين أيضًا.
Instead, he took me to the hospital with you.
وبدلًا من ذلك، أخذني معك إلى المستشفى.
Doesn't that prove that he likes you?
ألا يثبت هذا أنه يحبك؟
He gave me the snake I wanted...
لقد أعطاني الثعبان الذي أردته...
because he knew...
لأنه كان يعلم...
I was doing it to save Chi Cheng's snakes.
لقد فعلت ذلك لإنقاذ ثعابين تشي تشنغ.
He took you to the hospital...
لقد أخذك إلى المستشفى...
because he didn't want Chi Cheng to feel anxious.
لأنه لم يكن يريد أن يشعر تشي تشنغ بالقلق.
Look.
ينظر.
It's obvious.
إنه واضح.
I'm not the one he likes.
أنا لست الشخص الذي يحبه.
What are you trying to say?
ماذا تحاول أن تقول؟
I think...
أظن...
Guo Cheng Yu likes Chi Cheng.
Guo Cheng Yu يحب Chi Cheng.
The snakes I asked for back then...
الثعابين التي طلبتها في ذلك الوقت...
were all rare species.
كانت كلها أنواع نادرة.
Guo Cheng Yu has...
قوه تشينغ يو لديه...
whatever snake Chi Cheng has.
أيا كان الثعبان الذي يملكه تشي تشنغ.
Also,
أيضًا،
it's exactly like the snake garden Chi Cheng has.
إنه يشبه تمامًا حديقة الثعابين التي يملكها تشي تشنغ.
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
For every snake Chi Cheng has,
لكل ثعبان يمتلكه تشي تشنغ،
Young Master Guo has a copy.
السيد الشاب قوه لديه نسخة.
Shut up.
اسكت.
Do you know why?
هل تعلم لماذا؟
Also,
أيضًا،
don't you think...
ألا تعتقد...
their love triangle...
مثلث حبهم...
is a bit strange?
هل هو غريب بعض الشيء؟
Strange?
غريب؟
What's strange about it?
ما الغريب في ذلك؟
They've been fighting for seven years...
لقد كانوا يقاتلون لمدة سبع سنوات...
because of Wang Shuo.
بسبب وانغ شوو.
But have you heard anyone...
ولكن هل سمعت أحدا...
look for Wang Shuo during those seven years?
هل كنت تبحث عن وانغ شوو خلال تلك السنوات السبع؟
Chi Cheng didn't...
تشي تشنغ لم يفعل...
because he hates him.
لأنه يكرهه.
But why didn't Guo Cheng Yu look for him?
ولكن لماذا لم يبحث عنه قوه تشنغ يو؟
I guess that makes sense.
أعتقد أن هذا منطقي.
If Guo Cheng Yu really liked Wang Shuo,
إذا كان Guo Cheng Yu يحب Wang Shuo حقًا،
they should have gotten together back then.
كان ينبغي عليهم أن يجتمعوا معًا في ذلك الوقت.
That's where the issue lies.
وهنا تكمن المشكلة.
Not only didn't Guo Cheng Yu get together with Wang Shuo,
لم يجتمع قوه تشنغ يو مع وانغ شوو فحسب،
he thought of all sorts of reasons to compete with Chi Cheng.
لقد فكر في كل أنواع الأسباب للتنافس مع تشي تشنغ.
So you think...
فهل تعتقد...
Guo Cheng Yu likes Chi Cheng?
هل غوو تشينغ يو يحب تشي تشينغ؟
That's not all.
هذا ليس كل شئ.
I also noticed...
لقد لاحظت أيضا...
that on the day we took the snakes,
أنه في اليوم الذي أخذنا فيه الثعابين،
when Guo Cheng Yu and Chi Cheng were fighting,
عندما كان قوه تشنغ يو وتشي تشنغ يتقاتلان،
Chi Cheng was clearly winning.
كان تشي تشنغ فائزًا بوضوح.
When he was about to punch Guo Cheng Yu in the face,
عندما كان على وشك لكمة Guo Cheng Yu في الوجه،
why...
لماذا...
couldn't he do it?
ألا يستطيع فعل ذلك؟
That's not right.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
Why are you saying Chi Cheng couldn't do it?
لماذا تقول أن تشي تشنغ لا يستطيع فعل ذلك؟
What are you trying to say?
ماذا تحاول أن تقول؟
I think...
أظن...
Chi Cheng...
تشي تشينغ ...
likes Guo Cheng Yu too.
يحب Guo Cheng Yu أيضًا.
Xiao Shuai.
شياو شواي.
Chi Cheng...
تشي تشينغ ...
and I...
وأنا...
I get it now.
لقد فهمت الآن.
You just want to prove...
تريد فقط أن تثبت...
that Guo Cheng Yu doesn't like you.
أن قوه تشنغ يو لا يحبك.
That's why you're being so creative...
لهذا السبب أنت مبدع جدًا...
that you're vividly imagining things.
أنك تتخيل الأشياء بوضوح.
It's because you're still inexperienced.
هذا لأنك لا تزال عديم الخبرة.
You'll understand in the future.
سوف تفهم ذلك في المستقبل.
Here.
هنا.
Have some milk. It's good for your brain.
تناول بعض الحليب، فهو مفيد لعقلك.
Xiao Chi.
شياو تشي.
Thank you for today.
شكرا لك على اليوم.
You spent so much time going to the hospital with me.
لقد قضيت وقتًا طويلاً في الذهاب إلى المستشفى معي.
Mrs. Wu, you really don't have to thank me.
السيدة وو، ليس عليك حقًا أن تشكريني.
I'm Da Qiong's colleague.
أنا زميل دا تشيونغ.
I should help you.
ينبغي لي أن أساعدك.
Here.
هنا.
Have a seat.
خذ مقعدا.
Xiao Chi.
شياو تشي.
Let me ask you.
دعني أسألك.
Is Da Qiong...
هل دا كيونغ...
performing well in the company?
أداء جيد في الشركة؟
Yes.
نعم.
Have some water, Mrs. Wu.
خذ بعض الماء، السيدة وو.
The company's boss...
رئيس الشركة...
really likes him.
يحبه حقا.
Da Qiong is an honest man.
دا تشيونغ رجل صادق.
He's not cunning.
إنه ليس ماكرًا.
In this day and age,
في هذا اليوم وهذا العصر،
honest people can't make a lot of money.
الأشخاص الصادقون لا يستطيعون كسب الكثير من المال.
They can only make a living.
لا يمكنهم سوى كسب لقمة العيش.
Da Qiong...
دا كيونغ ...
has long mutated.
لقد تحورت منذ فترة طويلة.
Xiao Chi.
شياو تشي.
Are you dating?
هل انت مواعدة؟
Yes.
نعم.
Young men like you...
شباب مثلك...
are the most likable.
هم الأكثر استحسانا.
You're bold in words and action.
أنت جريء في أقوالك وأفعالك.
Unlike Da Qiong.
على عكس دا تشيونغ.
He had a girlfriend for three years.
لقد كان لديه صديقة لمدة ثلاث سنوات.
And they broke up.
وانفصلا.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Shouldn't I feel anxious?
ألا ينبغي لي أن أشعر بالقلق؟
He had a girlfriend for three years?
هل كان لديه صديقة لمدة ثلاث سنوات؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Look.
ينظر.
Da Qiong even sent me a photo of them before.
حتى أن دا تشيونغ أرسل لي صورة لهم من قبل.
I'll find it for you.
سأجده لك.
(Da Qiong)
(دا تشيونغ)
Why... Why can't I find it anymore?
لماذا... لماذا لم أعد أستطيع العثور عليه؟
Mrs. Wu, the photo is not important.
السيدة وو، الصورة ليست مهمة.
They dated for so long.
لقد كانا يتواعدان لفترة طويلة.
Why did they break up?
لماذا انفصلوا؟
Da Qiong told me...
أخبرني دا كيونغ...
they're not compatible.
إنهم غير متوافقين.
I know in my heart...
أنا أعلم في قلبي...
that the girl...
أن الفتاة...
dislikes us for being poor.
يكرهنا لكوننا فقراء.
At that time,
في ذلك الوقت،
they were already talking about marriage.
وكانوا يتحدثون بالفعل عن الزواج.
She was already at the door,
لقد كانت بالفعل عند الباب،
but she went home.
لكنها ذهبت إلى منزلها.
After that,
بعد ذلك،
Da Qiong...
دا كيونغ ...
never mentioned her to me again.
ولم يذكرها لي مرة أخرى.
Mrs. Wu.
السيدة وو.
It's all in the past now.
لقد أصبح كل ذلك في الماضي الآن.
Don't think about it anymore.
لا تفكر في هذا الأمر بعد الآن.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
these are the medicines.
هذه هي الأدوية.
This one must be taken three times a day.
ينبغي أن تؤخذ هذه الجرعة ثلاث مرات في اليوم.
This one twice a day.
هذا مرتين في اليوم.
They're all taken after meals.
يتم تناولهم جميعا بعد الوجبات.
Well, get some rest first.
حسنًا، احصل على بعض الراحة أولًا.
I'll get going.
سأذهب.
- Okay? - Thank you.
-حسنا؟ - شكرا لك.
No worries, Mrs. Wu. I won't disturb you anymore.
لا تقلقي يا سيدتي وو، لن أزعجك بعد الآن.
I remember...
انا أتذكر...
Da Qiong sent me a photo.
أرسل لي دا تشيونغ صورة.
(Da Qiong)
(دا تشيونغ)
It's right here.
إنه هنا.
Get the medicines based on this.
احصل على الأدوية بناءً على هذا.
Just take it as prescribed.
فقط تناوله حسب الوصفة الطبية.
Dr. Jiang.
الدكتور جيانج.
Xiao Zhuang.
شياو تشوانغ.
I brought you some fruits.
لقد جلبت لك بعض الفواكه.
So it didn't leave a scar, right?
إذن لم يترك ندبة، أليس كذلك؟
Look. There's no trace of it anymore.
انظر، لم يعد هناك أي أثر له.
That's good. From now on, take good care of yourself.
هذا جيد. من الآن فصاعدًا، اعتني بنفسك جيدًا.
Stop thinking about that jerk.
توقف عن التفكير في هذا الأحمق.
What are you chatting about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
I'll go wash some fruits.
سأذهب لغسل بعض الفواكه.
Don't...
لا...
Dr. Jiang, why are you feeling shy?
الدكتور جيانج، لماذا تشعر بالخجل؟
Who?
من؟
Who's feeling shy?
من يشعر بالخجل؟
You have bad eyesight, don't you?
هل لديك ضعف في البصر؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm slow-witted.
أنا بطيء الفهم.
If you have bad eyesight,
إذا كان لديك ضعف في البصر،
go to a big hospital.
اذهب إلى مستشفى كبير.
Don't get a consultation here.
لا تحصل على استشارة هنا.
Do you know how troubled I've been in the past few days?
هل تعلم كم كنت مضطربًا في الأيام القليلة الماضية؟
I thought your ex-lover was coming back.
اعتقدت أن حبيبك السابق سيعود.
Do you know how upset I was?
هل تعلم كم كنت مستاءً؟
I'm a terrible person.
أنا شخص فظيع.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I've always thought you're a man...
لقد اعتقدت دائمًا أنك رجل...
who's magnanimous and broad-minded.
من هو كريم وواسع الأفق.
I didn't expect you to be such a hypocrite!
لم أتوقع أن تكون منافقًا إلى هذه الدرجة!
You instigated Jiang Xiao Shuai to trick me, didn't you?
لقد حرضت جيانغ شياو شواي على خداعي، أليس كذلك؟
Don't you ever lie?
هل لا تكذب أبدًا؟
Everyone makes mistakes.
الجميع يرتكبون أخطاء.
All right.
حسنًا.
I admit.
انا اعترف.
I approached you...
لقد اقتربت منك...
because of Yue Yue.
بسبب يو يو.
All right.
حسنًا.
We're even now.
نحن متعادلون الآن.
When he comes back later,
عندما يعود في وقت لاحق،
I'll officially attack him.
سأهاجمه رسميًا.
When he's utterly embarrassed,
عندما يشعر بالحرج الشديد،
I'll tell him why I approached him.
سأخبره لماذا اقتربت منه.
That way, I can show him my magnanimity...
بهذه الطريقة، أستطيع أن أظهر له شهامتي...
and braveness in taking responsibility as a man.
والشجاعة في تحمل المسؤولية كرجل.
That's what I'll do.
هذا ما سأفعله.
What's your pose for?
ما هو وضعك؟
Have you eaten?
هل أكلت؟
I haven't.
ليس لدي.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
I bought some food downstairs.
اشتريت بعض الطعام في الطابق السفلي.
Eat it while it's hot.
تناوله وهو ساخن.
No.
لا.
It's up to you if you'll eat or not.
يعتمد الأمر عليك إذا كنت ستأكل أم لا.
This won't do.
هذا لن يفعل.
I need to get into the mood.
أحتاج إلى الدخول في المزاج.
Here.
هنا.
Try it on.
جربه.
When did you buy it?
متى اشتريته؟
When I was buying clothes for my mom today,
عندما كنت أشتري ملابس لأمي اليوم،
I bought one for you too.
لقد اشتريت لك واحدة أيضاً.
Why didn't you buy it today,
لماذا لم تشتريه اليوم؟
of all days?
من كل الأيام؟
I was finally starting to get fired up.
لقد بدأت أخيرا في الشعور بالحماس.
This appeal to the emotions...
هذا النداء إلى العواطف...
blew out my fire.
أطفأت ناري.
I'm too softhearted.
أنا طيب القلب للغاية.
Are you done?
هل انتهيت؟
Yes.
نعم.
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
It fits you quite well.
إنها تناسبك جيدًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Don't take it off.
لا تخلعها.
Just wear it.
فقط ارتديها.
It's nice.
إنه لطيف.
I have good taste.
لدي ذوق جيد.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
- Did you meet Xiao Shuai? - Yes.
- هل التقيت بشياو شواي؟ - نعم.
Did he tell you...
هل أخبرك...
that I asked him to persuade you?
أنني طلبت منه أن يقنعك؟
Persuade?
يقنع؟
That's not persuasion, but manipulation!
هذا ليس إقناعًا، بل تلاعبًا!
So you think I'm a person who will do anything...
فهل تعتقد أنني شخص سيفعل أي شيء...
to get what I want, right?
للحصول على ما أريد، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
You said you'd be patient with me.
لقد قلت أنك سوف تكون صبورًا معي.
You said you wouldn't mind when I'll think things through.
قلت أنك لن تمانع عندما أفكر في الأمور.
And you said you wouldn't force me.
وقلت أنك لن تجبرني.
But you secretly threatened Jiang Xiao Shuai...
لكنك هددت سرا جيانغ شياو شواي ...
and forced him to make me do it.
وأجبرته على أن أجبرني على فعل ذلك.
Chi Cheng, I thought you were a man...
تشي تشنغ، اعتقدت أنك رجل...
who's magnanimous and broad-minded.
من هو كريم وواسع الأفق.
But I didn't expect you to be such a hypocrite!
ولكنني لم أتوقع أن تكون منافقًا إلى هذه الدرجة!
Do you know...
هل تعلم...
how troubled I've been in the past few days?
كم كنت مضطربًا في الأيام القليلة الماضية؟
I thought your ex-lover was coming back.
اعتقدت أن حبيبك السابق سيعود.
Do you know how upset I was in the past few days?
هل تعلم كم كنت منزعجًا في الأيام القليلة الماضية؟
You used such cheap tricks to provoke me...
لقد استخدمت مثل هذه الحيل الرخيصة لاستفزازني...
and built all your happiness...
وبنيت كل سعادتك...
on my pain.
على ألمي.
I regret it so much now.
أنا آسف جدًا الآن.
I shouldn't have listened to Jiang Xiao Shuai back then.
لا ينبغي لي أن أستمع إلى جيانغ شياو شواي في ذلك الوقت.
I should have ignored you back then!
كان ينبغي لي أن أتجاهلك في ذلك الوقت!
You were ridiculed so much.
لقد سُخر منك كثيرًا.
You can't take it anymore, right?
لا يمكنك تحمل ذلك بعد الآن، أليس كذلك؟
Come at me if you can.
تعال إلي إذا كنت تستطيع.
Curse me. Swear at me.
إلعنني. أقسم علي.
After that, I can show you my trump card.
بعد ذلك، أستطيع أن أريك ورقتي الرابحة.
I admit it.
أعترف بذلك.
It's all my fault.
إنه خطئي كله.
I was too impatient.
لقد كنت غير صبور للغاية.
I was afraid that if we delayed it too much,
كنت خائفة من أنه إذا تأخرنا كثيرًا،
you'd overthink it.
سوف تفكر في الأمر أكثر من اللازم.
I went to Jiang Xiao Shuai...
ذهبت إلى جيانغ شياو شواي...
because he knows you the best.
لأنه يعرفك جيدا.
That's why I used this method.
لهذا السبب استخدمت هذه الطريقة.
Of course,
بالطبع،
it was a bit too forceful.
لقد كان الأمر قويًا بعض الشيء.
I don't feel good about it either.
أنا لا أشعر بالارتياح حيال ذلك أيضًا.
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
Why doesn't he play by the rules?
لماذا لا يلعب حسب القواعد؟
How could I tell him about Yue Yue now?
كيف يمكنني أن أخبره عن يو يو الآن؟
If I come clean,
إذا جئت نظيفة،
will I end up worse than Wang Shuo?
هل سأكون أسوأ من وانغ شو؟
Are you still mad at me?
هل مازلت غاضبا مني؟
Do you...
هل أنت...
still hate Wang Shuo?
لا تزال تكره وانغ شو؟
Why are you bringing him up for no reason?
لماذا تذكره بدون سبب؟
Do you...
هل أنت...
care about him?
هل تهتم به؟
I told you.
أخبرتك.
What I care about is what happened back then,
ما يهمني هو ما حدث في ذلك الوقت،
not him.
ليس هو.
What if...
ماذا إذا...
he comes back and give you an explanation?
هل يعود ويقدم لك تفسيرا؟
Will you forgive him?
هل ستسامحه؟
No.
لا.
But what if he really had his reasons?
ولكن ماذا لو كان لديه أسبابه حقًا؟
What happened, happened.
ما حدث، حدث.
I, Chi Cheng,
أنا، تشي تشينغ،
hate it when people lie to me.
أكره عندما يكذب الناس علي.
I... I also...
أنا... أنا أيضا...
lied to you a lot, right?
كذبت عليك كثيرًا، أليس كذلك؟
But you didn't do anything to me.
ولكنك لم تفعل بي شيئا.
Within my control,
تحت سيطرتي،
those...
أولئك...
aren't lies.
ليست اكاذيب.
Just little schemes, at most.
مجرد مخططات صغيرة، على الأكثر.
But if it's beyond my control,
ولكن إذا كان الأمر خارجا عن سيطرتي،
and you keep me in the dark,
وأنت تبقيني في الظلام،
that's what you really call lying.
هذا ما تسميه الكذب حقا.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
What?
ماذا؟
Have you lied to me?
هل كذبت علي؟
How?
كيف؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I had an ulterior motive...
لقد كان لدي دافع خفي...
when I approached you back then.
عندما اقتربت منك حينها.
What ulterior motive?
ما هو الدافع الخفي؟
(Bonus Clip)
(مقطع إضافي)
Daily necessities?
الضروريات اليومية؟
But Sir,
ولكن سيدي،
does the essence you mentioned just now...
هل الجوهر الذي ذكرته للتو...
really work?
هل تعمل حقا؟
I'll buy a bottle for you to try.
سأشتري لك زجاجة لتجربها.
Just wait.
فقط انتظر.
You'll come in handy one day.
سوف تكون في متناول يديك يوما ما.